citycosmetics.com 2018-09-03

# City Beauty - Privacy Policy

### Overview:

City Beauty, LLC, d/b/a City Beauty® is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that children (i.e. anyone who is under the age of 18) are protected from adult materials. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcomed visitor to City Beauty®, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit www.citybeauty.com, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone (we never do!), and the choices you have regarding our use of, your ability to correct the information, and the option to opt out, if desired. 

### Information about You:

This website uses third party cookies to track data. This includes but is not limited to the Google AdWords remarketing service that advertises on third party websites to previous visitors of our site. Previous visitors may see our advertisements on the Google search results page, a site in the Google Display Network, or on another third-party vendors' network. Third-party vendors, including but not limited to Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our websites. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, or you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Names and emails entered by our visitors in the "First Time Customer Special" form is collected by our GetResponse Service. Visitors who register for the "First Time Customer Special" are opting into the City Beauty® mailing list for news and special offers, and visitors may opt out at any time.

Upon placing an order, City Beauty® will specifically ask for information about you. We will ask for your full name, billing address, telephone number, email, and credit card number in order to ship you your products and provide you with all of City Beauty®'s services. We use your telephone number only if there is an order- related issue, though because we understand your need for anonymity we will make all attempts to contact you via email. We do not use your telephone number for marketing purposes. We may email you promotional content related to your interaction on our site and/or reminders of pending purchases all to which you will have the option to opt out at your request. Our database stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to your City Beauty® personal page and make the appropriate changes or call our Customer Support Line at 1-800-347-1558. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to not respond. 

### Tracking Information:

City Beauty® will collect and store only the following non-personally identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the IP address associated with; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site. We also track your order and billing history so you can access your City Beauty® account and immediately determine which product you've purchased and how you paid for them. This information is password-protected. No one has access to it but you. As you browse the City Beauty® website, cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to track the items you select as you shop, and help us match your address and credit card information with your order so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our site. Cookies also allow us to gather information to provide you with the best service. It tells us the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site. The only party that we may share your transaction processing information is VeriSign, which subsequently may share that information to a third party licensor of the fraud prevention scoring services (the "Fraud Service Bureau") solely for use in developing its fraud prevention modeling and for performing the Fraud Services. All your transaction processing information provided to the Fraud Service Bureau shall be subject to written agreement between VeriSign and the Fraud Service Bureau restricting disclosure of any Customer Data to other third parties except as necessary to perform the Fraud Services, otherwise, all of your personal information such as name, address and telephone number will not be shared with any third parties.

Emails: We will never sell any of your personal information. We may share your email with third parties to perform services on your behalf. 

### Disclosure:

We do not share your personal information, as described above, to any third parties. We may however share with our Partners aggregated statistical information about the use of our website. Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name or address with a partner company will be done only with your permission. We use a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access. We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

### California Residents:

Many browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us by email at support@citybeauty.com or at the following mailing address:

**City Beauty®**  
9361 Canoga Avenue  
Chatsworth, CA 91311

Please specify in your communication that you are making a “California Shine the Light” inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days. 

### Children Policy:

We do not specifically market to children under the age of thirteen (13). Children may not use our services, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

### Privacy Policy Changes:

If we decide to change our privacy policy from City Beauty®, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please contact us if you have any questions concerning our privacy policy. We can be reached at support@citybeauty.com or, for immediate support, please call us from 5am-7pm PST Mon-Fri, and 6am-4:30pm PST Sat-Sun at 1-800-347-1558.

**City Beauty®**  
9361 Canoga Avenue  
Chatsworth, CA 91311  
1 (800) 347-1558  
support@citybeauty.com  

Effective date: 3/2/17
